moviesonclick.com 2011-10-28

# Privacy Policy | moviesonclick

Moviesonclick.com offers a well trusted privacy policy for its users. The policy describes in detail how the website uses and protects your information when you visit this website to ensure complete privacy. Understanding your need for privacy, all the information required by this website that may or may not reveal your identity is strictly covered under the privacy rules of this policy. So you need not worry about divulging any information that may reveal your identity.

Whenever you happen to visit MOC, your IP address and other such information is automatically received by our website from your browser every time you view some page or click on some link present on the website. We receive all the information about your browser type, IP address and location whether you visit our site through a computer, laptop, mobile phone etc., all this information gets registered with us.

Cookies are small files which are kept on your system’s hard drive upon getting permission. These cookies make web applications respond in a way like an individual by collecting and recalling all of your preferred information and content and then tailors its operations to those preferences.

Our website in an effort to constantly improvise our website as per the likes and dislikes of the viewers and visitors by studying data about the web page traffic use traffic log cookies to identify the most viewed pages and content. This use of information is strictly for statistical analysis purpose and is removed soon after use.

Though most web browsers have an inbuilt acceptance for cookies, you can actually modify your browser to reject cookies in case you don’t want them. However, by doing so, you will only stop yourself from using the full website to your benefit.

As our website is totally committed to securing and protecting your private information, you need not worry about any unauthorized access or disclosure of your valuable information. Certain physical, electronic and managerial procedures are employed by MOC to protect user’s data collected online from misuse.

Without prior permission from you or unless required by law, none of your private information can be sold, distributed or leased to third parties by MOC. Though in the user’s interest we may send promotional information about third parties using your personal data stored with us, you can at any point ask us to stop sending this information if you believe it to be incorrect or incomplete by writing to us an email as soon as possible.

Users need not worry about their financial information as no credit card information is saved permanently on MOC’s servers. All the financial information like credit card numbers and other such identifying financial data are SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted and are directly transmitted in SSL to the site which processes all MOC customers credit card orders.

Though MOC carries related links to other websites, we offer no responsibility of the user’s privacy once you happen to leave our website by clicking on the link to the other website. All those websites which though have their links on MOC, are not covered or governed under MOC privacy policy. You are therefore advised to be careful about divulging any private information on these websites by clicking on the links provided on MOC web pages.

All the MOC content displayed on MOC web pages is company’s property and cannot be republished, copied, printed or used in any way, on any medium and under any circumstances without prior permission from the company. For any other queries regarding privacy and use of personal and company’s information, feel free to contact @ info@moviesonclick.com

The privacy policy is revised from time to time in view of constant technical and other changes. So keep visiting this page you keep yourself updated regarding the latest policies.
